

CONTACT

- → hello@laurenlalita.com
- **** 707-243-3038
- **?** Sonoma County, CA
- **#** LINKEDIN:

linkedin.com/in/lauren-duker

- ⊕ GITHUB:
 - github.com/LaurenDarrimon
- **PORTFOLIO:**

laurendarrimon.github.io/lauren-duker-darrimon

PORTFOLIO

- Travel Company Site Build
- App of COVID sites

SKILLS

- Mobile first & responsive UI
- Full stack Javascript engineer
- UI/UX design
- Graphic design & branding
- Verbal & written communication

TOOLS

DEVELOPMENT: Javascript, HTML, CSS, SASS, JQuery, JSON, Vue.js, Bootstrap, Node.js

DESIGN: Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Figma, Wordpress, Squarespace

LAUREN DUKER DARRIMON

SUMMARY

Full stack engineer with experience in UI design. Skills in Javascript, CSS and HTML with strengths in problem solving and verbal communication.

Freelance web and graphic designer for 3 years. Delighted to develop responsive applications where the code is as beautiful as the UI.

EXPERIENCE

Web & Graphic Designer

Freelance | Aug 2019 - present

- Responsive websites for small businesses
- Branding & identity formulation
- Print & product label design

Web Designer, Webmaster, & Retreat Operations

Euphoria Retreats | Jan 2019 - Nov 2021

Design and travel company and website,

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp

University of California, Berkeley Extension Dec 2021 - Mar 2022, In progress

Web + Mobile Front End Development Certificate

Santa Rosa Junior College Jun 2021 - Dec 2021

B.S. Engineering Physics

Colorado School of Mines 2002 - 2007, Incomplete